You know, Baroness is about making combinations of thirteen.
Aces are worth one, kings are worth thirteen and we're doing math with all the values in between.
Now for this board, the only combination of thirteen that's available is this three plus one of the tens.
So I'm going to take the three plus this ten, that's thirteen.
And now I'm looking for other combinations that add up to thirteen.
Well a ten needs a three.
A two needs a jack because jacks are worth eleven.
An Ace is worth one, it needs a queen which is worth twelve.
So I have nothing that I can play.
But, don't be disheartened.
This game can make very nice runs.
You can actually move six or seven cards off in one turn.